Y'know, maybe it would've been better
if you came down here later.
I don't think there's anything to enjoy about
touring a school you're not applyin' for.
Well, you'd be wrong.
So, you're going to take the exam
to get into a school down here?
Of course I am. It's lookin' pretty
likely that I'll come back to Osaka, so far.
Huh. Did you just subtly reject me?
Let's be real, I've been more or less
rejecting you this entire time.
Never seems to sink in, though!
Oh, can I see your keys?
My keys?
I made a new one.
The one from yesterday
was basically ancient...
Kinda bums me out how much
my skills have fallen off.
Here, for you.
We're almost there, so let's get going.
I'd Rather You Hate Me than Not Care
Part Two
Alright, I'll see you all for
tomorrow's volunteering as well.
I'm glad I was able to find this place.
I'm no good with maps.
It's all thanks to you two.
If that's all you need, you can always ask.
And we can help with your thesis
research whenever. Right?
By the way, Nao, are you
coming out for drinks today?
Yeah. I plan to, why?
Well, Miku said something about you
coming home late this morning.
But it was probably for work, right?
Yeah.
Miku was talking about how she thought
you had a guy here in Osaka.
Of course not. How could I?
Well, I'll see you two tonight.
It's so stupid.
I'm not gonna get serious about
someone as toxic as him.
We are arriving at Fujito Women's
College, Fujito Women's College.
Excuse me! You're Shiota Nao-chan, right?
Whoa, it is you!
Wow, she's so cute in person!
Would it be okay if we took a pic with you?
Thanks so much!
Can you believe it?!
Hey, excuse me...
Do you have a second?
I'm so sorry!
Since those high schoolers
were talking to you,
I thought you were going to college here...
I've got a rotten sense of direction and
couldn't find the student affairs office.
Don't worry about it. I think it's
in the same direction I'm headed.
I'm used to people looking at me,
but she doesn't seem to care about how
she shapes up compared to other girls.
So nasty.
Did you travel from far away?
Nah, I'm from Osaka, but
I live in Tokyo at the moment.
I thought so.
I came from Tokyo too, and I thought
I had seen you somewhere before...
Maybe with someone I know.
You don't mean Miyama Kirishima, do you?
Th-That's right, Miyama-kun.
You seriously know Kirishima?
Well, just a bit.
She brings his name up that easily?
How stupid is she?
Have you...
Known Kirishima for long?
Oh, no, we're not that close.
But we attended the same grade school.
It was a private school called Minatohayama.
He already stood out way back then.
Does it have to do with his...
unique family circumstances?
So, she knows.
That was part of it, but Miyama-kun's
parents were normal people.
His parents?!
Oh, sorry, it's just... his
parents are still around?
I think they are.
Since it was a private
school, if they weren't...
Well, you know, I think there
would have been rumors.
I see. Actually, that makes sense.
He's got parents like anyone else, huh?
You seem to know a lot about him.
Oh no, Miyama-kun's just a bit famous.
After... everything that happened.
You mean that fight he got into?
Do you know the details about what happened?
Not particularly.
But there was a famous karate
dojo near the grade school,
and Miyama-kun was a student there.
But he got into a fight
with some classmates...
and injured them pretty badly, I believe.
I think that's it. I
should get going, anyway.
Oh, of course.
I really appreciate it.
It's okay. But if you could, don't
mention this to Miyama-kun.
You bet! Thanks again.
Bye, now.
Actually, one other thing...
Do you mind if I ask one last thing?
Didn't think she'd actually
give me her contact info.
It's pretty clearly a
burner account, though.
What is?
Do you know a girl named Shiota Nao?
Nah. Who's that?
She used to be on TV and
stuff. I ran into her...
Minatohayama Institute Grade School
Founded in 1927.
A unified school offering classes from
preschool to college. Highly regarded
by households looking for an integrated
education with a curriculum specializing
in helping to shape children to fit their
future needs...
Did something happen?
Nothing for you to worry about, relax.
You realize we're always together in Tokyo,
right? And it's been the same as usual.
You're going to tour the college
again tomorrow, right?
I'm gonna meet up with you in the
evening, since exams end tomorrow.
But that's...
Wait, you oughta be studying!
All you've been doing is snackin'!
I'll do fine.
Like hell, dumbass!
Oh, I was right about Kobe. Lucky me.
I might have a knack for real estate.
What now?
You wanna come with? Doesn't seem
like you're gonna be studying.
Where we going?
Kobe.
Somei Yoshino
She seems flashy on the surface,
but empty on the inside.
Kirishima-kun must have different
taste in women now.
Nao!
You feeling okay?
No, I'm okay. Thanks for worrying, Ozu-kun.
You've been avoiding me lately, haven't you?
Does it have to do with the rumors?
It's so messed up.
I mean, I did introduce her to those guys,
but you know how it is with girls and rumors...
It turned into a whole thing.
You can relate, right, Nao?
You've been having guys help
you with your thesis, right?
I didn't really ask them to.
You never do, do you, Nao?
But you still manage to control the guys
that come around in spite of that.
You can be kind of a creep,
sometimes, Ozu-kun.
We're not dating anymore, so I'd
appreciate it if you didn't bother me.
Hey, it was praise!
I make pretty good use of the girls
that are interested in me, too.
I didn't think she would bring
the cops into it, though.
Throwing away a chance to milk those
guys for cash. Can you imagine?
What are you talking about?
You heard the rumors, right?
About me forcing girls from the
agency to meet with guys I know.
It's the other way around, though.
I've been introducing wannabe actresses and
models who don't have any real prospects
to rich potential patrons and taking
a fee for making the connection.
If she had the guts to pull one
over on those rich idiots,
she could've leeched off of
them for the rest of her life.
What? Why are you telling me this?
You slept with Miyama Kirishima, right?
What?! Do you have me confused with someone?
I'm impressed.
Most women wouldn't have the guts to risk their
big newscaster job by going out with a yakuza.
I'm telling you, it wasn't me.
I've got pictures and video.
And you smoked marijuana while
you were in America, didn't you?
With a classmate from college,
in July, two years ago.
I-I did no such thing!
To be honest, it doesn't really
matter if you did or didn't,
or if you screwed that yakuza.
I can make it sound like you did
just because you were there.
What do you want me to do?
I'm glad you're fast to catch on!
You always were clever, Nao.
Tomorrow, I want you to bring Miyama
Kirishima to a specific location.
But don't let him realize what's going on.
Make sure that yakuza's granddaughter
he hangs out with is there, too.
You do that, and I'll make
all of this go away.
I have no idea who you're talking about!
She's the granddaughter of
a Kirigayama-gumi big shot.
I think it's the Somei boss.
I believe her name is Yoshino.
If you're feeling guilty about
selling your boy out, don't worry.
Miyama Kirishima himself was the one who
spread the rumors about you and him.
He sold you out.
At this point, regrets aren't
gonna get you anywhere,
so I'm counting on you.
Did you know that Mount Tenpo over
there is only five meters tall?
For real?! And I was psyched
about telling you.
I thought you were going to
tour the campus again today.
I figured it'd be fine to skip a day.
"Aquatic life showcase"?
It's an aquarium.
Huh, it's like we're on a date.
I can see the resemblance, I guess.
That'd be fine, though. An aquarium date.
That said... probably shouldn't have
come here during summer vacation.
Should we hold hands to keep from getting
separated? Since it's a date and all.
Please, no. I only said
that I saw a resemblance.
I guess that's true.
Did you come here often?
This place is sorta the local aquarium.
I used to think all of them were called
aquatic life showcases until I was in second grade.
That's adorable.
That's just how it goes when you're a kid.
I'm not so sure.
I don't remember anything like that.
What, like you don't remember your
childhood? Some kinda amnesia?
Don't be silly. I remember it.
But there isn't anything entertaining
enough to tell you about.
So, tell me something
that isn't entertaining.
Stuff like food or hobbies...
or your birthday.
Are you seriously interested in that stuff?
If you don't wanna talk
about it, that's fine.
Come to think of it, I never
told you my birthday.
April 2nd.
That was so fast it was creepy.
As for favorite foods, I'd say
Wakayama ramen, sanuki udon,
mitarashi dango, and sakura mochi...
And most things with sweet cream on 'em.
Don't really have a lot of
hobbies, but I do like driving.
Great for blowing off steam.
You have a license?
Huh, so you don't know everything about me.
I knew that you got a learner's
permit during spring break.
Okay, but why?
I should probably get my license too.
But it's not gonna be for a while.
Since my birthday's not for four months.
Four months? So you were born in November?
I guess so.
I dunno why, but I can't help but be
suspicious about everything you say.
I guess that makes you a
Scorpio? Or a Sagittarius?
Well, which is it?
A Scorpio, I guess.
Seriously? I'm an Aries, they're supposed
to be a terrible match for Scorpios.
Really? What would be a good match?
Gemini, I think.
Okay, in that case, my birthday is in June.
How's that supposed to work?!
Sorry, sorry. It really is in November.
I'll take care of that.
Thanks, Ozu-kun.
Wait, Shiota Nao didn't show?
She supposedly isn't feeling well.
Seriously? That's hilarious.
Why'd that chick even come to Osaka?
Come on, that's going overboard.
Do you like sharks?
Grandpa wants me to send
him pics whenever I go out.
Am I in the way?
Nah, it's fine!
S-Scary... does this dude have
eyes in the back of his head?
When did you first get a girlfriend?
Just asking.
Either sixth grade or the
first year of middle school.
But she was more like a
patron than a girlfriend.
I had an arrangement with the boss
where he only gave me a certain
amount of money to cover my food.
Which meant I usually didn't eat my fill,
so until the second year of middle school,
I'd look for people with money...
Dude, you were a gigolo.
I was. But I really never dated a girl
from the same class or anything.
We attended the same grade school.
He didn't say anything about
the same school, huh?
You're asking a lot of questions today.
Hobbies, favorite foods... It's like
a meeting for an arranged marriage.
I mean, that's kinda why I was askin'.
Those kinda things are normal
to ask first, aren't they?
It's honestly weird that we skipped them.
I absolutely don't plan on marrying you,
but it wouldn't be fair to
just stay ignorant, either.
I don't care anymore, though.
You might not lie, but you're
not exactly honest, are you?
Although that does fit
what I do know about you.
Let's just wait out the remaining
eight months, doing what we're doing.
Hey!
I...
Your phone.
Sorry. I should have put it on silent.
Would you mind waiting here?
Sudden business, huh?
Yeah. Something came up, apparently.
How about you come straight home, too?
What sudden business?
Considerin' he's in Osaka.
No clue...
You want me to stake out the apartment
building? I'm closer to Kobe.
One new message
Yoshino-san?
Nah. I'll go.
I started this, so I'll take care of it.
Is this what I think it is? Again?
Why, you got a problem?
Nothin' but problems, yeah.
Why do you even care what his deal is?
If he dies, he's got it comin',
so just let him bite it.
That's awful kind of you.
"Kind"? You sure you're not the one
gettin' attached, Yoshino-san?
Don't be stupid. I could give a rat's
ass about what he does and with who.
The thing is... before this wraps up,
I've gotta kick his ass a few times.
If he's gonna die, it's gotta be after that.
I play nice for a little while and
everyone thinks they can clown on me...
I'll talk to you later.
Yoshino-sa—
Makeup time.
You seem down today.
No. I'm okay.
I'm sorry. I know you were busy today.
It's fine. You're more important.
More than her? Somei Yoshino?
I ran into her yesterday at Fujito Women's U.
Surprised?
No, I knew.
I didn't expect you to trade
contact info, though.
You actually gave her yours? Did you
think it'd come in handy some day?
How do you know about that?
Did you arrange for us to meet?!
No. But I did anticipate that
you might run into each other.
Although ideally, you would've
seen the two of us together.
You heard from Ozu Kento, right?
I was relieved when you contacted me.
This would've been a huge waste
if you had gotten attached
enough to me to turn him down.
But when you're selling out a
scumbag, there's no guilt, right?
Wait... did you let me see
that picture on purpose?
I figured you would look.
Sending a message to myself
ended up paying off.
Unbelievable... You're all such
scum, I wish you'd just die!
Those rumors about you
were true, weren't they?
What rumors?
That girl at the agency who went
into porn before disappearing
and how you were involved.
Oh, that.
You and Ozu will do anything
for money, won't you?!
You're probably working together!
You really ended up being the
perfect mark for Ozu-kun.
It's true that I told him we were
going out, albeit indirectly.
And I did know the girl you mentioned.
But Ozu-kun was the one involved
in her disappearance, not me.
Being surrounded by worthless
people can wear anyone out.
Her depression had gotten particularly bad,
and she mentioned going home to see
her parents three months ago.
But she told me a month later how she was
excited to be working for a new agency.
I tried to convince her
to work somewhere else,
but never managed get a hold
of her... Then came the porn.
And then the disappearance.
And you're saying Ozu Kento was responsible?
The same thing has happened to three
girls I know in the last few months.
You're the fourth.
What did Ozu-kun say to
get you to come here?
That he'd get rid of the evidence
of us being together
if I bring you to a specific location...
Anything about marijuana?
Then he would've been able to blackmail
you, even if I wasn't involved.
He was after you all along.
He'd been getting on my nerves
lately, but that was just because
his backers happened to share that
particular interest with him...
They're using Ozu, and he's using you.
You're gonna be his bitch for the
rest of your life, at this rate.
Then what am I supposed to do?!
This only happened because
you used me to lure him out!
It would've been even worse for
you if I hadn't, trust me.
Besides, it goes both ways.
I was dating you in order to establish
connections with the people you knew.
And you wanted me for my connections,
as well as the convenient violence
that the yakuza offer.
So, let's get going. Where
did Ozu-kun want to meet?
What about that Yoshino girl?
She's already headed there.
What are you talking about?
The deal was for me to bring her, too.
I contacted her already, saying
I had something to tell her.
No, you didn't.
I did! I can show you.
I've got a copy of her phone,
so I can tell when she gets a text.
I sent the text to a tablet, not a phone.
She asked me specifically
to contact her through it.
She sent the friend request
to me yesterday.
Hey, Kirishima?
What are you doing there?
Look, just listen.
You're with Shiota Nao, right?
Ozu Kento isn't at the location
she wanted me to go to.
What do you mean?
Because right now...
I'm looking at him.